<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Higher Education on Study In Taiwan</title>
    <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/tags/higher-education/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Higher Education on Study In Taiwan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://studyintaiwan.github.io/tags/higher-education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Founder of StudyInTaiwan</title>
      <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/team/</guid>
      <description>Founder of StudyInTaiwan Welcome to StudyInTaiwan, founded by Pavan Kumar MP, your ultimate destination for navigating the higher education landscape in Taiwan.&#xA;About Me I am Pavan Kumar MP, a final-year Ph.D. candidate in the Department of Computer Science and Engineering at National Sun Yat-sen University, under the guidance of Professor Kun Chih (Jimmy) Chen. Currently, I am engaged in an enriching research internship at NCHC (國家高速網路與計算中心), Tainan, where I am fortunate to work under the mentorship of Dr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Services for Students Pursuing Higher Studies in Taiwan</title>
      <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/community/</guid>
      <description>Services for Students Pursuing Higher Studies in Taiwan Are you considering pursuing your bachelor&amp;rsquo;s, master&amp;rsquo;s, or Ph.D. studies in Taiwan? We offer comprehensive services tailored to your needs and aimed at making your transition to Taiwanese universities seamless and efficient.&#xA;STEP 1: Initial Consultation In this step, we provide you with valuable insights into the current conditions in Taiwan and assess your specific requirements. Through an audio/video call, we discuss your aspirations and concerns, offering personalized advice to kickstart your journey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Services for Students Pursuing Higher Studies in Taiwan</title>
      <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/service/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/service/</guid>
      <description>Services for Students Pursuing Higher Studies in Taiwan Are you considering pursuing your bachelor&amp;rsquo;s, master&amp;rsquo;s, or Ph.D. studies in Taiwan? We offer comprehensive services tailored to your needs and aimed at making your transition to Taiwanese universities seamless and efficient.&#xA;STEP 1: Initial Consultation In this step, we provide you with valuable insights into the current conditions in Taiwan and assess your specific requirements. Through an audio/video call, we discuss your aspirations and concerns, offering personalized advice to kickstart your journey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Higher Education System in Taiwan</title>
      <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/edusystem/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 19:53:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/edusystem/</guid>
      <description>Higher Education System Taiwan boasts an excellent global competitiveness despite limited natural resources. According to the World Competitiveness Yearbook 2019 published by the International Institute for Management Development (IMD) in Switzerland, Taiwan ranked 16th overall in global competitiveness among 63 countries, excelling in &amp;ldquo;Economic Performance&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Business Efficiency Indices.&amp;rdquo; This economic prowess is attributed to Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s high-quality human resources, which are closely linked to the quality of its higher education system.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
