<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Study In Taiwan</title>
    <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Study In Taiwan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 19:53:33 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://studyintaiwan.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>7-Step Guide for International Students</title>
      <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/steps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 19:53:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/steps/</guid>
      <description>Study in Taiwan: A 7-Step Guide for International Students Introduction Studying in Taiwan offers numerous opportunities for international students seeking quality education in a vibrant cultural environment. This guide presents a step-by-step approach to help prospective students navigate the application process effectively.&#xA;Step 1: Eligibility Assessment Before proceeding with your application, ensure that you meet the eligibility criteria for international students as per the MOE Regulations Regarding International Students Undertaking Studies in Taiwan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Education at a Glance 10 Reasons to Study in Taiwan</title>
      <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/glance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 19:53:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/glance/</guid>
      <description>Education at a Glance Taiwan has an outstanding higher education system that provides opportunities for international students to study a wide variety of subjects, ranging from Mandarin Chinese language and history to tropical agriculture and forestry, genetic engineering, business, semi-conductors, and more. In Taiwan, we hold education and scholarship in high regard, so you will experience a vibrant, modern society rooted in one of the world’s most fascinating cultures, and populated by some of the friendliest and most hospitable people in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eligibility Requirements for International Students Applying to Taiwanese Universities</title>
      <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/eligibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 19:53:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/eligibility/</guid>
      <description>Eligibility Requirements for International Students Introduction When applying for admission to universities in Taiwan as an international student, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to understand the eligibility requirements and application procedures. This guide provides comprehensive information to help prospective students navigate the process.&#xA;Requirements Overview There are various pathways to apply for admission, depending on the desired subject of study and the applicant&amp;rsquo;s background. It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that requirements and deadlines may differ between universities and degree programs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Founder of StudyInTaiwan</title>
      <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 19:53:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/team/</guid>
      <description>Founder of StudyInTaiwan Welcome to StudyInTaiwan, founded by Pavan Kumar MP, your ultimate destination for navigating the higher education landscape in Taiwan.&#xA;About Me I am Pavan Kumar MP, a final-year Ph.D. candidate in the Department of Computer Science and Engineering at National Sun Yat-sen University, under the guidance of Professor Kun Chih (Jimmy) Chen. Currently, I am engaged in an enriching research internship at NCHC (國家高速網路與計算中心), Tainan, where I am fortunate to work under the mentorship of Dr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 19:53:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/faq/</guid>
      <description>Q1: Am I eligible to apply as an international student? You will be eligible as an international student if you fulfill the following 3 conditions:&#xA;You have foreign nationality and have never studied in Taiwan before as an overseas Chinese student at the time of application. You have never been admitted through admission placement by the University Entrance Committee for Overseas Chinese Student at the time of application. You must apply in accordance with the &amp;ldquo;Regulations Regarding International Students Undertaking Studies in Taiwan&amp;rdquo; by the Ministry of Education (MOE).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Higher Education System in Taiwan</title>
      <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/edusystem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 19:53:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/edusystem/</guid>
      <description>Higher Education System Taiwan boasts an excellent global competitiveness despite limited natural resources. According to the World Competitiveness Yearbook 2019 published by the International Institute for Management Development (IMD) in Switzerland, Taiwan ranked 16th overall in global competitiveness among 63 countries, excelling in &amp;ldquo;Economic Performance&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Business Efficiency Indices.&amp;rdquo; This economic prowess is attributed to Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s high-quality human resources, which are closely linked to the quality of its higher education system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Housing Options for International Students in Taiwan</title>
      <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/housing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 19:53:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/housing/</guid>
      <description>HOUSING ON-CAMPUS HOUSING Living in a dormitory provided by the university is often the most convenient option for international students. Here are some advantages and considerations:&#xA;Advantages:&#xA;Proximity to the school. Cost-effective. Enhanced safety. Considerations:&#xA;Shared living space with roommates. Limited space and facilities. Availability may vary, so contact the university&amp;rsquo;s international office beforehand. PRIVATE ACCOMMODATION Renting off-campus provides more flexibility but comes with its own set of considerations:&#xA;Advantages:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List of Taiwanese Universities by Ranking</title>
      <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/uni/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 19:53:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/uni/</guid>
      <description>Title: List of Taiwanese Universities by Ranking Ranking University Name Location Website 1 National Taiwan University Taipei City Visit 2 National Yang Ming Chiao Tung University Taipei City Visit 3 National Taiwan Normal University Taipei City Visit 4 National Tsing Hua University Hsinchu Visit 5 National Cheng Kung University Tainan City Visit 6 National Chengchi University Taipei City Visit 7 Tamkang University New Taipei City Visit 8 National Central University Taoyuan City Visit 9 National Sun Yat-Sen University Kaohsiung City Visit 10 Chinese Culture University Taipei City Visit 11 National Chung Hsing University Taichung City Visit 12 Fu Jen Catholic University New Taipei City Visit 13 National Kaohsiung University of Science and Technology Kaohsiung City Visit 14 National Chung Cheng University Minxiong Visit 15 Feng Chia University Taichung City Visit 16 National Taiwan University of Science and Technology Taipei City Visit 17 China Medical University, Taiwan Taichung City Visit 18 I-Shou University Kaohsiung City Visit 19 Taipei Medical University Taipei City Visit 20 Tunghai University Taichung City Visit 21 Soochow University, Taiwan Taipei City Visit 22 National Taipei University of Technology Taipei City Visit 23 Ming Chuan University Taipei City Visit 24 National Dong Hwa University Shoufeng Visit 25 Providence University Taichung City Visit 26 National Taiwan Ocean University Keelung Visit 27 National Chi Nan University Puli Visit 28 National Yunlin University of Science and Technology Douliu Visit 29 Chung Yuan Christian University Taoyuan City Visit 30 Yuan Ze University Taoyuan City Visit 31 Kaohsiung Medical University Kaohsiung City Visit 32 National Changhua University of Education Changhua Visit 33 National Taipei University Taipei City Visit 34 Chaoyang University of Technology Taichung City Visit 35 Southern Taiwan University of Science and Technology Tainan City Visit 36 Tatung University Taipei City Visit 37 Asia University, Taiwan Taichung City Visit 38 Chang Gung University Taoyuan City Visit 39 Shih Hsin University Taipei City Visit 40 National University of Kaohsiung Kaohsiung City Visit 41 National Chiayi University Chiayi Visit 42 Chung Hua University Hsinchu Visit 43 National Formosa University Huwei Visit 44 National Pingtung University of Science and Technology Pingtung City Visit 45 National Taiwan University of Arts New Taipei City Visit 46 National Kaohsiung Normal University Kaohsiung City Visit 47 Taipei National University of the Arts Taipei City Visit 48 National Pingtung University Pingtung City Visit 49 Shih Chien University Taipei City Visit 50 Tzu Chi University Hualien Visit 51 National Taipei University of Education Taipei City Visit 52 Nanhua University Dalin Visit 53 National Taichung University of Education Taichung City Visit 54 National University of Tainan Tainan City Visit 55 Chung Shan Medical University Taichung City Visit 56 Wenzao Ursuline University of Languages Kaohsiung City Visit 57 National Taitung University Taitung Visit 58 Chang Jung Christian University Tainan City Visit 59 Da-Yeh University Dacun Visit 60 National Ilan University Yilan City Visit 61 Kun Shan University Tainan City Visit 62 University of Taipei Taipei City Visit 63 Cheng Shiu University Kaohsiung City Visit 64 Nan Kai University of Technology Caotun Visit 65 Aletheia University Taipei City Visit 66 Shu-Te University Kaohsiung City Visit 67 National United University Miaoli Visit 68 Dharma Drum Institute of Liberal Arts New Taipei City Visit 69 Hungkuang University Taichung City Visit 70 Minghsin University of Science and Technology Xinfeng Visit 71 National Taichung University of Science and Technology Taichung City Visit 72 Huafan University New Taipei City Visit 73 Fo Guang University Jiaosi Visit 74 Lunghwa University of Science and Technology Taoyuan City Visit 75 Fooyin University Kaohsiung City Visit 76 Hsuan Chuang University Hsinchu Visit 77 Chien Hsin University of Science and Technology Taoyuan City Visit 78 Kainan University Taoyuan City Visit 79 Chia Nan University of Pharmacy and Science Tainan City Visit 80 Tainan University of Technology Tainan City Visit 81 National Chin-Yi University of Technology Taichung City Visit 82 Yu Da University of Science and Technology Zaoqiao Visit 83 Vanung University Taoyuan City Visit 84 National Taipei University of Nursing and Health Sciences Taipei City Visit 85 Central Taiwan University of Science and Technology Taichung City Visit 86 Tainan National University of the Arts Tainan City Visit 87 Tajen University Yanpu Visit 88 Chihlee University of Technology New Taipei City Visit 89 China University of Technology Taipei City Visit 90 Yuanpei University Hsinchu Visit 91 Takming University of Science and Technology Taipei City Visit 92 Hsiuping University of Science and Technology Taichung City Visit 93 Ming Chi University of Technology New Taipei City Visit 94 Kao Yuan University Kaohsiung City Visit 95 National Taiwan University of Sport Taichung City Visit 96 National Taipei University of Business Taipei City Visit 97 National Kaohsiung University of Hospitality and Tourism Kaohsiung City Visit 98 China University of Science and Technology Taipei City Visit 99 Jinwen University of Science and Technology Taipei City Visit 100 CTBC Financial Management College Tainan City Visit 101 MingDao University Pitou Visit 102 Asia Eastern University of Science and Technology New Taipei City Visit 103 National Quemoy University Jinning Visit 104 Tungnan University New Taipei City Visit 105 Tzu Chi University of Science and Technology Hualien Visit 106 National Taiwan Sport University Taoyuan City Visit 107 National Penghu University of Science and Technology Magong Visit 108 Hwa Hsia University of Technology New Taipei City Visit 109 St John&amp;rsquo;s University Taipei City Visit 110 Chang Gung University of Science and Technology Taoyuan City Visit 111 Ling Tung University Taichung City Visit 112 Chienkuo Technology University Changhua Visit 113 Overseas Chinese University Taichung City Visit 114 Tung Fang Design of University Kaohsiung City Visit 115 Meiho University Pingtung City Visit 116 Minth University of Science and Technology Qionglin Visit 117 Chung Hwa University of Medical Technology Tainan City Visit 118 WuFeng University Minxiong Visit 119 Taipei City University of Science and Technology Taipei City Visit 120 Far East University Tainan City Visit 121 Nanya Institute of Technology Taoyuan City Visit 122 Taipei University of Maritime Technology Taipei City Visit 123 University of Kang Ning Tainan City Visit 124 TransWorld University Douliu Visit 125 HungKuo Delin University of Technology New Taipei City Visit 126 Chung Chou University of Science and Technology Yuanlin Visit 127 Deh Yu College of Nursing and Health Keelung Visit 128 Hsing Wu University New Taipei City Visit 129 Lee-Ming Institute of Technology New Taipei City Visit 130 Tatung Institute of Commerce and Technology Chiayi Visit 131 Dahan Institute of Technology Xincheng Visit 132 Taiwan Shoufu University Tainan City Visit 133 National Taiwan College of Performing Arts Taipei City Visit 134 Chungyu University of Film and Arts Technology Keelung Visit 135 Toko University Puzi Visit 136 Fortune Institute of Technology Kaohsiung City Visit 137 Lan Yang Institute of Technology Toucheng Visit 138 Nan Jeon University of Science and Technology Tainan City Visit Credits: UniRank</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Money and Cost of Living in Taiwan</title>
      <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/money/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 19:53:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/money/</guid>
      <description>MONEY AND COST CURRENCY The official currency of Taiwan is the New Taiwan dollar (TWD). Key points about the currency:&#xA;Currency code: TWD Abbreviations: NT$, NTD$ Common denominations: NT$100, NT$500, NT$1000 bills; NT$50, NT$10, NT$5, NT$1 coins Cash payment is prevalent, with credit cards, Easy Card, and iPass also widely accepted. AVERAGE EXPENDITURE IN TAIWAN Average monthly expenditure in major cities (for reference only):&#xA;Taipei: NT$28,550 New Taipei City: NT$22,419 Taichung: NT$23,267 Kaohsiung: NT$21,674 Tainan: NT$19,536 TUITION FEES Tuition fees in Taiwan vary depending on the program and university:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quick Facts About Taiwan</title>
      <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/quickfacts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 19:53:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/quickfacts/</guid>
      <description>Where is Taiwan? Taiwan and its surrounding islands are situated in East Asia at the northwestern edge of the Pacific Ocean. It possesses an endless variety of terrains, forests, agricultural products, and marine ecologies, as well as a diversity of ethnic cultures along with enchanting human customs and practices.&#xA;Location: Taiwan is located off the eastern and southeastern coasts of the Asian continent, between Japan and the Philippines. It measures approximately 400 kilometers from north to south and around 145 kilometers from east to west at its widest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan Fellowships &amp; Scholarships</title>
      <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/gscholar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 19:53:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/gscholar/</guid>
      <description>GOVERNMENT SCHOLARSHIP The Taiwan Fellowships &amp;amp; Scholarships (TAFS) program is a Republic of China (R.O.C.) government initiative aimed to promote relevant research, educational links, and enduring friendships between Taiwan and the global community.&#xA;The TAFS comprises 8 awards in 3 categories: Fellowships for research, Huayu (Mandarin) Enrichment Scholarships, and Scholarships for Degree. Approximately 1,200 grants are provided annually for undergraduate and postgraduate students as well as researchers across the world to study or to conduct advanced research in Taiwan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visa Information for Students in Taiwan</title>
      <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 19:53:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/visa/</guid>
      <description>VISA In Taiwan, there is no specific &amp;ldquo;Student Visa&amp;rdquo; category. Instead, foreign students can apply for either a Visitor Visa or a Resident Visa, depending on the duration of their program.&#xA;Types of Visa Visitor Visa: Suitable for stays of less than 6 months. Resident Visa: Required for programs lasting longer than 6 months. Taiwan (ROC) Embassies and Missions Abroad Taiwan has over 109 embassies and missions in 73 countries. Students should contact the nearest Taiwanese embassy or mission in their country for visa application.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List of Available Mentors to Guide You</title>
      <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/mentors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/mentors/</guid>
      <description>List of Available Mentors Here is a list of mentors currently available to guide you through your journey of studying in Taiwan:&#xA;Note: With whom you talk, the money will be credited to them.&#xA;Mentor Name University Department Contact Pavan Kumar MP NSYSU, Kaohsiung Taiwan Department CSE LinkedIn [Mentor 2 Name] [University Name] [Department Name] [Contact Information] [Mentor 3 Name] [University Name] [Department Name] [Contact Information] [Mentor 4 Name] [University Name] [Department Name] [Contact Information] [Mentor 5 Name] [University Name] [Department Name] [Contact Information] </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Services for Students Pursuing Higher Studies in Taiwan</title>
      <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/service/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/service/</guid>
      <description>Services for Students Pursuing Higher Studies in Taiwan Are you considering pursuing your bachelor&amp;rsquo;s, master&amp;rsquo;s, or Ph.D. studies in Taiwan? We offer comprehensive services tailored to your needs and aimed at making your transition to Taiwanese universities seamless and efficient.&#xA;STEP 1: Initial Consultation In this step, we provide you with valuable insights into the current conditions in Taiwan and assess your specific requirements. Through an audio/video call, we discuss your aspirations and concerns, offering personalized advice to kickstart your journey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STEP 1: Initital Consultation</title>
      <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/step1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/step1/</guid>
      <description>In this step, we provide you with valuable insights into the current conditions in Taiwan and assess your specific requirements. Through an audio/video call, we discuss your aspirations and concerns, offering personalized advice to kickstart your journey.&#xA;Service Fee:&#xA;₹1000 INR / ~400 NTD (Equivalent to 6 Cups of Coffee in FamilyMart) We need you to fill the Google form by filling the required field, so that we can know more about your requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STEP 2: Application Guidance</title>
      <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/step2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/step2/</guid>
      <description>Congratulations on completing Step 1 of your journey towards higher education in Taiwan! Now, let&amp;rsquo;s delve into Step 2: Application Guidance, where we equip you with the knowledge and tools necessary to navigate the application process with confidence.&#xA;Service Fee:&#xA;₹30,000 INR How We Help You in STEP 2: Step Number What We Offer STEP 2 Stage 1 Profile Evaluation ✔️ Stage 2 Shortlist Major &amp;amp; University ✔️ Stage 3 Shortlist Professors &amp;amp; Schedule Interviews ✔️ Stage 4 Assistance with Application Process ✔️ Stage 5 Document Preparation For Application ✔️ Stage 6 Get information about stipend &amp;amp; scholarship ❌ Stage 7 Avail fee waivers &amp;amp; prestigious scholarships ❌ Stage 8 Accept ❌ STEP 1: Profile Evaluation We begin by thoroughly evaluating your academic profile, extracurricular activities, and personal achievements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STEP 3: Comprehensive Admission Assistance</title>
      <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/step3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/step3/</guid>
      <description>For those seeking hands-on support throughout the admission process, our team offers comprehensive guidance at every stage. From application submission to document preparation and beyond, we&amp;rsquo;ll be by your side, ensuring a smooth and successful admission experience.&#xA;Service Fee:&#xA;₹60,000 INR How We Help You in STEP 3: Step Number What We Offer STEP 2 STEP 3 Stage 1 Profile Evaluation ✔️ ✔️ Stage 2 Shortlist Major &amp;amp; University ✔️ ✔️ Stage 3 Shortlist Professors &amp;amp; Schedule Interviews ✔️ ✔️ Stage 4 Assistance with Application Process ✔️ ✔️ Stage 5 Document Preparation For Application ✔️ ✔️ Stage 6 Get information about stipend &amp;amp; scholarship ❌ ✔️ Stage 7 Avail fee waivers &amp;amp; prestigious scholarships ❌ ✔️ Stage 8 Accept ❌ ✔️ STEP 1: Profile Evaluation We begin by thoroughly evaluating your academic profile, extracurricular activities, and personal achievements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/post/2020-12-01-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/post/2020-12-01-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.&#xA;You can embed an R code chunk like this:&#xA;summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
