<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Study Abroad on Study In Taiwan</title>
    <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/tags/study-abroad/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Study Abroad on Study In Taiwan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 19:53:33 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://studyintaiwan.github.io/tags/study-abroad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>7-Step Guide for International Students</title>
      <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/steps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 19:53:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/steps/</guid>
      <description>Study in Taiwan: A 7-Step Guide for International Students Introduction Studying in Taiwan offers numerous opportunities for international students seeking quality education in a vibrant cultural environment. This guide presents a step-by-step approach to help prospective students navigate the application process effectively.&#xA;Step 1: Eligibility Assessment Before proceeding with your application, ensure that you meet the eligibility criteria for international students as per the MOE Regulations Regarding International Students Undertaking Studies in Taiwan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Education at a Glance 10 Reasons to Study in Taiwan</title>
      <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/glance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 19:53:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/blogs/glance/</guid>
      <description>Education at a Glance Taiwan has an outstanding higher education system that provides opportunities for international students to study a wide variety of subjects, ranging from Mandarin Chinese language and history to tropical agriculture and forestry, genetic engineering, business, semi-conductors, and more. In Taiwan, we hold education and scholarship in high regard, so you will experience a vibrant, modern society rooted in one of the world’s most fascinating cultures, and populated by some of the friendliest and most hospitable people in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Founder of StudyInTaiwan</title>
      <link>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 19:53:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://studyintaiwan.github.io/team/</guid>
      <description>Founder of StudyInTaiwan Welcome to StudyInTaiwan, founded by Pavan Kumar MP, your ultimate destination for navigating the higher education landscape in Taiwan.&#xA;About Me I am Pavan Kumar MP, a final-year Ph.D. candidate in the Department of Computer Science and Engineering at National Sun Yat-sen University, under the guidance of Professor Kun Chih (Jimmy) Chen. Currently, I am engaged in an enriching research internship at NCHC (國家高速網路與計算中心), Tainan, where I am fortunate to work under the mentorship of Dr.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
